canvaspeople.com 2012-06-24

# Canvas People

### Terms of Use

I hereby affirm that I own the copyright to the photo or digital image provided to CanvasPeople.com or I am authorized by the owner of the copyright to the photo or digital image to use the photo or digital image for any purpose and agree to indemnify CanvasPeople for all costs and expenses in the event a third party claim is asserted with respect to the ownership rights in the photo or digital image. Once the photo or digital image is altered by CanvasPeople, it becomes property of CanvasPeople. I agree to hold CanvasPeople harmless for any damages or loss to the photos or digital image. Upon placing an order, I agree to have CanvasPeople adjust my order on my behalf in the event that the order cannot be completed in a manner that CanvasPeople deems necessary to ensure customer satisfaction.

Images on the CanvasPeople site may not be accurate. Art received via mail may vary in color from images on the website.

Delivery charges will be covered by you (customer). CanvasPeople.com cannot guarantee delivery times or dates due to circumstances beyond their control.

I hereby release CanvasPeople and any of its associated or affiliated companies, their directors, officers, agents, employees and customers, and appointed advertising agencies, their directors, officers, agents and employees from all claims of every kind related to the alteration of the photos or digital images.

I further consent to the reproduction and/or authorization by CanvasPeople, to reproduce and use said photographs for use in all domestic and foreign markets. Further, I understand that others, with or without my consent, may use and/or reproduce such photographs. In addition, by participating, I am agreeing to the use of my photo or likeness for publicity, marketing, and sale purposes with no financial or other type of compensation. I hereby waive any right to inspect or approve any publicity materials produced. These publicity materials may be used at the discretion of CanvasPeople and any of its associated or affiliated companies, their directors, officers, agents, employees and customers, and appointed advertising agencies, their directors, officers, agents and employees. 

Canvas People reserves the right to refuse to print an item to canvas.

CanvasPeople/ Parent Media Group, Inc. reserves the right to refuse to fill any order for a product if that product would bear a customer image that consists or may consist, in CanvasPeople's sole discretion and determination, in whole or in part of:

  1. an image, character, text or other content protected by copyright and owned by a party other than Parent Media Group, Inc. or the customer submitting the image;
  2. a trademark, service mark, logo or slogan owned by a party other than Parent Media Group, Inc. or the customer submitting the image;
  3. any other intellectual property owned by a party other than Parent Media Group, Inc. or the customer submitting the image, or
  4. any image, text or other content that is profane, vulgar, obscene, pornographic, graphically sexual or contains nudity; or
  5. any image, text or other content that is threatening, harassing, defamatory, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable; or
  6. any other material which may give rise to civil or criminal liability under any applicable law.

The customer agrees to fully indemnify and hold Parent Media Group, Inc. harmless of, from and against any liability, loss, damages, costs and attorneys fees that may be alleged against or incurred by Parent Media Group, Inc. as a result of any and all claims by third parties or law authorities related in any manner to customer images or Parent Media Group, Inc.’s manufacture of or fulfillment of orders for products bearing customer images regardless of whether or not Parent Media Group, Inc. pre-screens the customer images.

### Copyright and Trademark Notice

This Site and its contents, including but not limited to, text, photographs, graphics, illustrations, video, sound and other material (all such content collectively referred to as "Content") are protected under United States and international copyright laws and are the property of CanvasPeople.com (A Parent Media Group, Inc. company) or its third party licensors. All rights reserved. All logos, splash screens, page headers, custom graphics and button icons displayed on this Site are service marks, trademarks, and/or trade dress (collectively, "Marks") of CanvasPeople or its third party licensors. Except as specifically permitted herein, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, modifying, selling or participating in the sale of, or otherwise exploiting or using any Content or any Marks in any form or by any means without the express written permission of CanvasPeople is prohibited and may violate the copyright or trademark laws of the United States and/or other countries.

The Site and its Contents are intended solely for personal, noncommercial use by the users of our Site. You may download or copy the Contents displayed on the Site for your own use provided that you maintain any notices contained in the Content, such as all copyright notices, trademark legends or other proprietary rights notices. In using downloaded materials, copyright and trademark notices shall be displayed and used in the manner shown or specified. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. No reproduction of any part of this Site may be sold or distributed for commercial gain nor shall it be modified or incorporated in any other work, publication, or website. CanvasPeople shall have no liability or any responsibility whatsoever for any loss suffered caused by viruses that may infect your computer equipment or other property by reason of your use of, access to or downloading of any material from this Site. If you choose to download material from this Site you do so at your own risk. 

### Privacy Policy

This website is maintained by CanvasPeople.com (A Parent Media Group, Inc. company). CanvasPeople recognizes the importance of privacy to our visitors. We understand that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information. Therefore, we've developed a formal privacy policy to assure you that we carefully protect customer information. We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time, so please check back occasionally.

You can reach us 24 hours a day, 7 days a week by sending an e-mail to (e-mail address) or by calling (phone #). If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: CanvasPeople, (mailing address). We will be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.

**OUR POLICY**  
We do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly at CanvasPeople.com. If you are simply browsing our website and learning about our products, we invite you to do so. As an unregistered visitor to our site, we'll recognize your home server (e.g., that your web access is through AOL.com), but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information.

We send all of our canvas orders through the mail, so if you wish to order our products, it will be necessary for you to provide personally identifiable information. This includes your name, address, phone number and, if you place your order online, credit card information. Any personal information you provide is downloaded off of the web server to a secure system and is maintained there.

**OUR CUSTOMER LIST**  
When you purchase items from our website, your name will be added to our Customer List. We will not share your email address with any third parties unless you are specifically asked to agree on the site. If you prefer not to receive mailings from us, please advise us by using the mail, phone or e-mail address provided above. Please include your name and address if you are contacting us by mail or e-mail. We will ensure that your name is promptly removed from the list.

**CONTACTS FROM US**  
If you have provided us with your e-mail address, we may notify you from time to time about CanvasPeople products or related services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive these e-mail notifications, please follow the "Opt-out" instructions included with the e-mail or contact us at (e-mail address).

**COOKIES**  
Like most internet-based companies, we use "cookies" (small pieces of information stored on your computer) on certain parts of our website. These cookies allow us to manage your session. This ensures that we keep your order saved while you browse through the site and select items for purchase. We do not use the cookie to collect any type of personal information, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer.

**SECURITY ONLINE  
**Most of our forms, especially when ordering a product or using online customer service, use secure pages to insure that the information sent between your computer and our system is secure. This is especially true if we are asking you for payment information.
